Now I see.
What's up, Robin? Did you find something?
I just determined the culprit that stole your memories.
Consequently, it's not the one we thought it was.
Wait a second. You mean it's not that little brat?
Now, let's make our way to the Sea God's Palace.
Sea God's Palace?
Okay, but why?
Just a hunch.
Zoro bears his fangs. A savage animal stands in the way.
So that little brat's hideout is just up ahead?
That's right.
Come on, who's the real thief here, Robin?
Isn't it about time you told us about whoever's behind all this?
Everything will become clear once we reach the Sea God's Palace.
They're up to something.
They're going to take me deep into the jungle, lock me up, and then steal my gold.
Oh, no!
Is this place really his hideout?
Seems pretty peaceful to me.
That's what he wants you to think.
Don't let your guard down.
I bet he has an army of crazy monsters hiding around here, just waiting for the chance to pounce on us.
What? Crazy monsters?
Yeah, monsters are known to disguise themselves to look like their surroundings, and then...
They sneak up, attack you, and gobble you whole.
That's right. See?
When you sail across the seas as many times as I have, you run into plenty of monsters.
You become aware of where they're likely to be.
Behind you! Look out!
What? Let me guess.
There's a monster behind you.
That trick's not going to work on...
Get it off me! Get it off me! Get it off me!
Please! You gotta do something!
Get it off me! Get it off me!
What are those two doing back there?
Come back! It's not a monster! It's a snake!
Get it off me, please! Somebody help me!
Get it off me! Get it off me!
Get it off me!
Uh... finally.
Guess I showed that snake a thing or two!
It fled in terror from the mighty Captain Usopp!
Hey!
We got separated from the others! What are we gonna do now, you stupid jerk?
Oh! Oh, crap!
Those crazy monsters are gonna find us! They're gonna find us and eat us!
Oh, I wouldn't worry too much.
I was just joking around about that and trying to scare you a little bit.
I was only kidding, okay?
It was a joke. Good.
What are you trying to do, huh? Give me a heartache!
Ah! Crazy monsters!
You said you were kidding!
Please don't eat me, Mr. Monster!
Eat this delicious raccoon dog instead!
No! Stop it!
Oh, it's just the swordsman. Don't scare us like that, okay?
Great! That maniac decided to come back!
Wonderful!
He seems different somehow.
He's not the same as he was back on the ship.
So, I take it you've changed your mind, huh?
Well, if you agree to straighten up and swear your loyalty to me,
I wouldn't mind bringing you on as one of the great Captain Usopp's...
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Where you going?
Wait, please!
Can you tell us where the others are?
Huh?
Whoa! Come back!
Don't leave me out here all alone!
Ha ha ha ha!
Hey!
Wait up!
Huh?
Look who we found!
Hey, Zorro!
Oh, great. It's the swordsman again.
Hmm? Hold on.
Decide to rejoin us, then?
Watch out!
Be careful, Captain!
Huh? What's wrong?
He's dead!
Close one!
Hey, Zorro! What the heck did you do that for?
Huh?
Stop it right now, both of you!
Wait, I don't think that's such a good idea.
Something's wrong with him.
He's acting completely different than he was on the ship yesterday.
Don't tell me he's...
Ah!
That's kind of dangerous.
You should stop.
Ah!
It's falling this way!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where's that straw hat guy?
You sure are being reckless
So, uh, I guess asking you to stop is a waste of breath, huh?
What the heck is up with that guy? He's pissed
It looks to me like he's under some form of hypnosis
I bet that kid did it
Well, that's a pain, right, listen up
We all need to work together and stop him, got it?
Stay out of it
You guys go on ahead
I'll take care of him
All right then, let's get going, come on
No way, he's not really going to take on Zoro the pirate hunter all by himself
In other words, no matter what, stopping him isn't going to happen
Right, capturing that boy is our priority
We'll have to leave this to the captain
Come, come!
Is that how he's gonna stop him? I thought those two were friends
If someone were to get hit with a punch like that, it would probably kill them
Because the swordsman's his friend
Because the captain knows his opponent's strength
He knows he cannot stop him unless he fights with everything he's got
Everything he's got, huh?
I can't believe I've been traveling with such dangerous people
Now, come on, let's hurry
I'll leave everything in your capable hands, Zoro
Free sword style
All right, let's run
Hmph.
Pony.
Get him!
Wait!
To be continued...
A sniper, and me, a navigator.
With that crew, there'd be no problem sailing the ship ourselves.
Hey guys, wait.
Are you really gonna go along with whatever that woman tells you?
She's a pirate, remember?
Pirates are all the same.
They're greedy, devious, and sneaky lowlifes.
Don't you get it?
Luffy and this woman have been lying to us from the beginning.
It's about time you realized it.
Leave now and come with me.
If you do, I promise to take you anywhere in the world you want to go.
You guys want to go back home to all of your family and friends, don't you?
I know you do.
I feel the exact same way.
There's somewhere that I have to return to.
Now that I think about it, I have no idea where these guys plan on taking me.
It might be safer if I travel with her instead of these freaks of nature.
You're right.
It's the same for me.
See?
Then what's there to think about?
Come on, let's go!
I really can't blame you for not putting your trust in me since you've lost your memory.
But whether you believe me or not, I ask that you follow me.
Aha!
What did I tell you?
Did you hear what she said?
She's lying to us!
Listen.
We all have dreams we want to fulfill on this sea.
Don't be so stupid!
People can't live just sailing around the world chasing their dreams and doing whatever the hell they want.
Come on, give me a break!
Maybe.
But tell me something.
What could be more important than chasing your dream?
Let's chase our dreams together.
Nothing in the world is more fun than that.
If our captain were here now, that's what he'd say.
I'm...
I'm gonna go with Nami.
Come on, let's all go back to our homes.
What do you say?
I'm...
I'm staying here with Luffy.
But why?
Because Luffy called me his...
He called me his friend and accepted me just the way I am.
The exact same way that Dr. Heroic and Dr. Ian did before.
Either way, be it go back home or chase my dream, there's something I need to take care of.
I'm not gonna be satisfied until I catch that brat and teach him a lesson.
That's happening first.
I don't believe this.
And with that matter being settled, I'm going on ahead.
All right, you two, shall we?
Aw, Tim at all.
There's no point in going home without my memory.
I've got to find some way to get it back.
What?
Hey, wait!
Fine, then.
I'll just sail out of this dump on my own.
My gold!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Three-sword style.
Ogi.
Now come go!
Five-sword!
Three-thousand worlds!
Sometimes strange and unexplained things happen here on the Grand Line.
Things like sailors being fine one minute, then suddenly losing their memories during a voyage.
I'm sure you've both heard stories like that before.
You think that same sort of phenomenon is happening on this island?
On that stone monument we passed on the way here, there was a story inscribed about a monster who lives off of people's memories.
It's said it's made this island its home.
It's practically a legend, but that is the explanation that seems to make the most sense.
Since new memories are created every day, this creature must be consuming the memories of the people of this island little by little.
I see. So it's kind of like raising a broiler.
I'm having a hard time buying that story.
But either way, our missing memories are at stake here.
We need to get to the bottom of this.
Stop right there!
Pirates just don't know when to quit, do they?
I'm going to manipulate all of you, just like I did that swordsman, and have you annihilate each other.
Oh no!
Looks like you'll be first.
It's not really my style to kick a kid, Putt.
Wait! It's not the boy!
Oh!
Where? How did? What happened?
Somebody stole our memories.
Was it you?
Mr. Cook, that little boy was just being manipulated.
The real thief here is...
Hold it right there!
If you think you're leaving without giving back every last memory you stole from us, you've got another thing coming, got it?
Listen, I went to a lot of trouble to get all these memories.
I'm not giving them back, you idiot!
What?
The good doctor can understand what animals say.
Look, don't give me any of that crap, you stupid octopus!
Ripple-boop-boop-boop-boop-boop-boop-boop-boop-boop!
You ignorant jerk, I'm not an octopus, I'm a seahorse, got it? That's what he said, not me.
It doesn't matter what you are, you little thief!
Hey! It's you!
Hurry up and cough up the rest of our memories or I'll fry you!
What the? What happened?
I'm not done with you yet.
Not by a long shot!
Sanji!
My memories!
We got all of our memories back!
Mr. Cook, what about you?
Of course I got them back!
My lovely Robin, my stunning Nami!
You're both breathtakingly beautiful,
with or without my memories!
But...
we don't know if that moss-headed swordsman
got his memories back or not.
Yeah, you're right.
If he didn't, then what are we gonna do?
Zoro!
Where's Luffy?
Wait, you don't...
You don't think that Zoro killed him, do you?
No...
It can't be!
What happened to the captain?
Now listen up!
If you plan on hurting these ladies,
then you're gonna have to go through me to do it!
Bim-pah!
He said I still haven't played my trump card yet!
Yeah!
掴み掛けた夢の欠片
変わらないもの
掘ってる僕らは
憧れを空に浮かべて
eh- nah-
Answering me,
e-
Hallo!
bodyguard
dh-
The last counter attack by the memory thief who revealed his true colors.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!